It's been a long time since I've come.
久しぶり、来ちゃった
Yui-chan!
ユイちゃんちゃん!
long time no see!
久しぶり!
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Did you come?
来てくれたの?
Because I'm back here.
こっちに戻ってきたから
I've been wanting to meet you.
会いたいなって思ってきて
Why Suzun?
なんでスーズンなの?
There were various circumstances, we met various people,
色々と諸事情があって、 色々と会って、
It's super cute.
超かわいいじゃん
I really wanted to meet you.
めっちゃ会いたかったんだよ
It really suits you.
めっちゃ似合ってんじゃん
I thought maybe we should get together again.
また集活しようかなって思って
He became a caster.
キャスターになってたじゃん
That's true, but we met many times and didn't meet again.
そうなんだけど、 色々と会って会わなくて、
Didn't we meet?
会わなかったの?
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
Something's wrong with me.
なんか やばい、俺
what?
何?
It might not stop.
止まんないかもしれない
Isn't it early?
早くない?
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
early?
早い?
I mean, are you happy?
だってさ、 嬉しい?
You came to see me, right?
会いに来てくれたんでしょ?
terrible.
やばい
It's been a long time.
超久々
terrible.
やばい
It's been a while though.
久々なんだけど
It's here.
来ちゃった
It's getting worse.
やばくなってきちゃった
Hmm, come on.
うーん、さあ
what?
何?
Oh no, already.
やばい、もう
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Sue
ス ー
It also looks great on you.
ズ ンめっちゃ似合うのもなってる
why?
なんで?
Didn't you send me a photo?
写真送らなかったっけ?
You sent it to me.
送ってくれたよね
Sent.
送った
what?
何?
What are you doing?
何してんの?
How have you been?
元気だった?
I was fine.
元気だった
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You communicated with me often.
よく連絡くれてたもんね
Well, that's it.
まあ、それはね
Just watch some TV.
ちょっとテレビを見ててよ
Why are you watching?
なんで見てんの?
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
It only appeared about three times.
3回くらいしか出てなかったよね
Yes, it only appears a little.
そう、ちょっとしか出てない
I fell asleep.
寝ちゃったな
It's kind of scary.
やばい、なんか
I'm so excited.
めっちゃ興奮する
It tickled.
くすぐった
Did it tickle?
くすぐった?
Did you come in with your shoes on already?
もう、靴のまま入ってきちゃったの?
I mean, keep your shoes on.
だって、靴のままで
Leave your shoes on.
靴のままで
Okay, keep your shoes on.
いいよ、靴のままで
Legs are fine.
足、いいよ
Open your legs.
足開いて
picture?
え?
shoes.
靴
It's not good.
良 くないし
Because it's Japan.
日本だからね
It's the best.
最高じゃん
It gets a little wrinkled.
ちょっとシワになっちゃうの
Will it get wrinkled?
シワになっちゃう?
It gets wrinkled.
シワになっちゃう
What are you doing?
何してんの?
picture?
え?
It's the best.
最高じゃん
picture?
え?
That's what I said.
って言ったよ
Hey, hey, hey.
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ
Hey.
ねぇ
Young, young.
若い、若い
Because, to me.
だって、僕に
Not to me.
僕にじゃない
Isn't this meant to be broken?
これ破くためにあるんじゃないの?
No.
違うよ
Long time no see.
久々
It's been a while since I saw it.
久々に見た
Don't look too closely.
あんた、じっくり見ないで
a little bit.
ちょっと
What are you doing?
何すんの?
Long time no see video.
映像に久々
painful.
苦しい
shoes.
靴
It's been too long.
久々すぎて
No more.
もう さ
Go to sleep.
寝よ
what?
何?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
Have you had sex with anyone since then?
あれから誰かとエッチしたの?
What are you doing?
してんの?
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
It moves slowly.
ゆっくり動くね
copper?
どう?
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言ってね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Wow, it's been a while.
すごい、久々
It's been a while since I saw it.
久々に見た
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Long time no see.
久々
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
terrible.
やばい
Just something.
ちょっと 何か
I couldn't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなっていっちゃった
good?
いい?
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
good?
いい?
sorry.
ごめん
I'm already too excited.
もう興奮すぎて
Because I thought I'd never see you again.
もう会えないと思ってたから
Sorry, Stocky drank it.
ごめん、ストッキーに飲めちゃって
cute.
可愛い
Sorry about that earlier.
ごめんね、さっき
Okay though.
いいけど
I'm worried.
悩んでる
I can't stand it.
我慢できないってさ
It's been a long time since we met and we got really cute.
久々に会っててめっちゃ可愛くなったね
That's a lie.
嘘だ
I don't think it has changed.
変わってないと思って
It turned out really cute.
めっちゃ可愛くなった
It suits you.
似合ってるし
A suit.
スーツが
It's not said much.
あんまり言われないよ
I haven't heard much about it though.
あんまり言われたことないけど
Really?
本当に?
It's tough on the weekends.
大変なんだ、週末とか
It's tough.
大変だね
I was flopping around in my unfamiliar shoes.
慣れないくつでバタバタバタバタ
That's right.
そうだよね
Do you live here?
こっち暮らすの?
Yeah.
うん
This way, forever.
こっちかな、ずっと
Living alone?
一人暮らしで?
Yes, I live alone.
そう、一人暮らしで
So, things are very difficult.
じゃあ、いろいろ大変なんだね
It's true.
本当だよ
I'll just have to do it myself.
ちょっと自分でやんなきゃ
here we go.
さあ
Shall we go to the room again?
もう 一回部屋に行こうか
Okay.
いいよ
real?
本当の?
No way.
いやー
So cute again.
改めてめっちゃ可愛い
TRUE.
本当
It hurt so bad.
すげー痛かったんだよね
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
But, you were a caster, right?
でもさ、 キャスターやってたでしょ?
You did it.
やってたね
Yeah.
うん
Have you stopped?
やめちゃったの?
Oh, relationships?
あ、人間関係?
After all, it was a complicated human relationship, wasn't it?
結構やっぱ、複雑な人間関係だったわけ?
That's right.
そうだ
I want to sell more.
もっと売りたいな
Glade and things like that.
グレイドとか、そういうのが
oh.
おー
So, I was a little shocked that it was different from what I had.
で、ちょっと 持ってたのと違ったなって ちょっとショック受
It's happening now.
けて る、今
Wait, you're like a producer?
え、そのなんか プロデューサーさんみたいな?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Are you forcing me to have a physical relationship with you?
体の関係を迫ってくるわけ?
Like adults on TV.
テレビで大人みたいな
You hear about celebrities a lot, right?
芸能人とかはさ、 結構聞いたりするじゃん?
There have been some conversations about this recently.
最近もなんかね、 そう いう話あったりしたけど
I didn't think I had it.
自分にあると思わなかったし
Is that why you were so strict?
そういうので厳密しちゃったってこと?
I will.
するね
Are you also a caster?
キャスターでもあるの?
Like.
みたいな
No, that's a terrible story.
いや、それはひどい話だよね
Actually, at first I thought of singing.
ほんとね、最初 歌ってやろうかと思ったもん
teeth?
は?
That's what I thought.
って思って
Well, it was just a dream.
それでまぁ、夢だったけど
I agree.
そうだね
I don't know what to say, but...
なんか もう、え、でも なんて言うんだろう、
When I quit, it wasn't like I was quitting or something like that.
別に辞めるときは そんななんか いやいや辞めるとかじゃなくて
If this is the case, then it's my own way to get a job.
こん なんだったら 別の、ちゃんと出職について 自分のやりか
I feel like I want to do something.
たい ことやりたいな みたいな感じで
That's what it was.
そういうことだったんだもん
The best thing is to do what you want to do in the environment you want to do it.
自分のやりたい環境で やりたいことやるのが一番いいもん
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Do you want to explain it because you like something?
ものが好きだから、説明に 言わしたいのか
nice.
いいね
Mental care time gathering
心のケアタイム 集達とか
I agree.
そうだ ね
So, are you having any interviews now?
じゃあ今、面接一体してんの?
Interview... That's right.
面接… そうだね
But I really wrote a resume and sent it.
でもほんと履歴書書かいて 送って、
Face... Is it an interview after passing the documents?
面… 書類とおったら面接?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うん うん うん
Do you go there often?
結構行ってる?
I'm on my way.
行ってるねー
Already, but there's this thing called corona after all, so I have to come to people.
もう、でもね やっぱコロナっていうのもあって 人に来ちゃ
That's why it's difficult.
ってる から難しいねー
It's pretty tough.
結 構厳しいんだ
What kind of job do you want to get? I quite like talking to people,
どういう職業につきたい 人と話すのが結構好きだし、
I like interacting with customers, so I like to work on customer service and just think about plans.
接するのが好きだから接客とか、まあ普通に企画考えたりっていう
I thought it would be fun too, so I'm doing that too.
の も楽しそうだなと思ってそちらの方もやってる
You're doing this seriously.
真面目にやってるんだね
I'm probably doing it seriously, which is rare.
珍しく真面目にやってるよ、多分ね
Finger is serious.
指ちゃん真面目だしね
I was feeling that serious, but just now...I'm sorry.
そんな深刻な感じだったのにさ、さっき...ごめんね
Pull it out and wonder what the shoes are.
引っ張って、靴って何だろうね
Well, I had Snipper written for me.
ちゃんとね、スニッパー書いてもらったけど
Sorry about the stockings.
ストッキングもうごめんね
I was surprised.
びっくりしたよ
Say something like “Biri”.
ビリッとか言って
I bought it properly.
ちゃんと買ってきたじゃん
I bought it.
買ってきたじゃん
Huh?
あれ?
pants?
パンツ?
It's not open right now.
開いてないよ、今
That's right.
そうだよね
I was completely soaked.
ビチョビチョになっちゃったもんね
They don't sell pants.
パンツ売ってないしね
I'll use this instead of the one I bought earlier.
さっき買ってきたやつさ、これ代わりにさ、
Just wear them.
履けばいいよ
You said you weren't wearing it just now.
今、履いてないって言ったよね
What?
何が?
You're not wearing them.
履いてないよね
I'm not wearing them right now.
私今、履いてないんですけど
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
pants?
パンツ?
Yeah.
うん
Do you wear stockings?
ストッキング履くの?
If you don't wear them, the suit won't fit you.
履かないとさ、スーツ合わないから
Would you like to try it on now?
ちょっと今、履いてみ?
I think the color sense is terrible.
色感やばいと思う
It's sexy when you wear it.
履くところってセクシーじゃん
Is that so?
そうなの?
I just want to see it.
ちょっと見たいんだよね
That's right.
そうだよね
At first it was quite torn myself.
最初自分でも結構破れてたからな
It's going to break after all.
やっぱ破れちゃうんだ
Even though I was in a hurry, it broke.
急いでんのに破けちゃった
Have you ever worn stockings without panties?
これノーパンでストッキング履いたことある?
There isn't.
ないよ
It's obvious, isn't it?
当たり前でしょ
There's no way that's the case.
あるわけないでしょ
Really.
本当に
I'm surprised.
びっくりだよ
Although it's less than the previous generation.
前代未満なんだけど
I can't see it at all.
全然見えないんだけど
全然見えないよ
You're hiding it, right?
隠してるでしょ
It's obvious.
当たり前じゃん
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
Some might even say it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいって言うのもあるけどさ
I can't stand this adult-like look.
こういう大人っぽい格好もたまんないね
I wonder what it feels like.
どんな感じなんだろう
I don't like it.
なんか嫌だな
I could wear it.
履けたじゃん
I was able to wear it though.
履けたけど
I'm not wearing them.
履いてないの
It feels so weird.
違和感すごい
Oh no this.
やだこれ
Stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立って
I don't like this.
これ嫌だ
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
I don't like this.
嫌だこれ
I really hate it.
めちゃめちゃ嫌だ
I can't help it.
しょうがない
Because my pants are dead.
パンツ死んじゃってるから
Who is to blame?
誰のせいですか
sorry.
ごめんなさい
This is nice.
これいいね
I think you'll pass this interview no matter where you go.
これどこの面接行っても受かると思うよ
There's no reason for that.
なわけないでしょ
No, really.
いや本当
And I don't watch it.
しかも見ないし
At the time of the interview.
面接の時
I can't see it.
見えません
to this point.
ここまで
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Can I have you turn around for a moment?
ちょっと後ろを向いてもらってもいい?
There are other ways to wear them like this.
こんな履き方もあるんだね
There isn't.
ないよ
ないのよ
I'd better go with this.
これで行ったほうがいいよ
I'm not going.
行かないよ
Well then, which one is it from earlier?
じゃあさ、さっきのさ、どれだ?
shoes?
靴?
shoes.
靴
Is this it?
これか
You'd better wear shoes.
靴履いたほうがいいよ
Look.
ほら
It looked great on me.
すごい似合ってた
Is it okay?
いいんのかな?
No.
いいや
That's good.
いいよね
Please sit down for a while.
ちょっと座ってくれんじゃん
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
I was really happy that you came to see me today.
今日会いに来てくれてすごく嬉しかったんだけど
Tell me I'll see you.
会 えるって言って
Someone I know really likes Yumi.
なんか俺の知り合いで、 ゆみちゃんのことがすげえ好きな人が
There are, right?
いる んだよね
Who is it now?
もう、誰?
It's probably someone you don't know.
知らない人だよね、多分
Hey, I'm taking pictures.
ちょっとあの、俺、撮ってるじゃん、
everytime.
いつも
I agree.
そうだね
I showed it to you.
見せちゃったんだけど
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Only that person.
その人だけね
I only showed him that person,
その人だけ見せちゃったんだけど、
Wow, I think I've fallen in love with it.
すごい、好きになっちゃったみたい
I feel like I'm in love with people.
人目ぼれみたい
I've been coming here every day, and I'm really having trouble getting a reaction.
毎日オナに来たようになって、 めっちゃリアクションに困ってる
Well then.
じゃ ん
That's a problem, right?
困るよ、そりゃ
I don't know anyone, so there's nothing I can do about it.
知らない人だからどうしようもないし
It's a person I don't know, but that person...
知らない人なんだけど、 その人なんか、
You said you wanted to meet me, and you just came today.
会いたいって言ってて、 今日ちょうど来てくれたじゃん、
Yumi-chan.
ゆみちゃん
So I thought it was just right.
だから、ちょうどいいかなと思った
Eh, so?
え、で?
I think I'll call you.
呼ぼうかなと
from now?
これから?
There's probably one nearby.
近 くに多分いるから
It's someone who lives nearby.
近くに住んでる人なんだけど
I mean, look, we're going to have an interview, right?
なんか、ほら、面接するわけでしょ?
I will.
するね
I think they will also practice for interviews, I guess.
面接の練習もしてくれると思う、多分
Ah, well, thank you.
あー、まあ、ありがたいけど
Because he has social experience.
社会経験もある人だから
Listen to that.
そういうの聞いて
good?
いい?
Hey, I've been asked a lot of questions.
ちょっと、すごい頼まれちゃってさ
I hope you don't like it.
嫌だったらいいんだけど
Well, that's fine though.
まあ、いいけど
It's a little uneasy.
ちょっと不安だよね
What I heard earlier.
さっきの聞いて
No, then, well, yeah.
いや、じゃあ、まあ、そうだね
Okay, well, that's it.
大丈夫、まあ、それは
It's okay, they say it's just rain.
大丈夫、そんな、別に雨だけって言わしてるから
It was okay.
大丈夫だったね
But, it's better not to say that you're brain-bun right now.
でも、その、今、脳パンであることは言わないほうがいい、
perhaps.
多分
I'll never say that.
絶対言わないよ
Really.
本当に
It's better not to say it.
言わないほうがいいね
Because it excites me.
興奮しちゃうから
Wait a minute, then I'll call you.
ちょっと、じゃあ、電話するわ
Wait a minute, then.
ちょっと、待って、じゃあ
Jemi called.
ジェミ、呼んだ
Did you call?
呼んだ?
lie?
嘘?
For lying to me.
嘘でくれて
I really like it.
めっちゃ好きなんだって
Yeah.
うん
get nervous?
緊張する?
It's obvious, isn't it?
当たり前でしょ
Seriously?
マジで?
Ah, it's here now.
あ、来ましたね、今
Oh, hello.
あ、どうも
Huh?
あれ?
Imi-chan?
イミちゃん?
yes.
はい
I heard you, Imi-chan.
あの、話聞いた、イミちゃん
Wow, it's Imi-chan.
わ ー、イミちゃんだー
real.
ほ んと
change.
変わる
Eh, ah, Chinese map.
え、あ、中華図で
Really?
本当に?
This was good, this.
これ、良かった、これ
Ah, ah, this.
あ、あ、これ
This, this, has changed.
これ、これ、変わって
Oh, you already touched me.
あ、 もう、お前触っちゃった
Smooth.
すべすべ
Oh, I did it.
え、やったー
I was able to meet you.
会えたよー
I wanted to meet you, Imi-chan.
会いたかったんだよね、イミちゃんに
That's right.
そうなんです
Wow, it's real.
うわ、本物だなー
Oh my gosh, I suddenly want to touch her before I get her consent.
やべ、もうね、承諾を得る前に、いきなり触りたくなっちゃう
That's what I mean.
っていう ね
Sorry, kinda.
ごめんなさい、なんか
I can't stand it.
我慢できなくて
It's real.
本物だ
I really like it.
すごい好きなの
すごい好きなのです
I'm wearing this when I'm job hunting.
これ着て、就活してるわけだ
Wow, that's it, wear this.
うわー、じゃあ、あれだよね、これ着てさ、
Because I do a lot of walking, etc.
いっぱい歩いたりとかするからさ、
It's soaked in sweat, too.
汗も染み込んでるわけだよね
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうですね
Oh, this?
あ、これ?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんです
Ah, all kinds of things.
あ、 い ろいろ
That's right.
そうなんですけど
Hey, isn't this something important?
あれ、ちょっとこれ、大事なやつなんじゃない?
Things like resumes.
履歴書とかさ
Can you please stop for a moment?
ちょっとやめてもらっていいですか?
Can I ask you to stop?
や めてもらっていいですか?
No, but I kind of like it.
いや、でもね、ちょっと好きだからさ、
After all, you want to see things about the person you like.
やっぱ好きな人のことって見たくなっちゃうじゃん
Eh, that's it now, right?
え、今あれでしょ?
Oh, I see, I'm going to have an interview and all that.
あ、そっかそっか、面接とかいろいろいってね、
Look at this.
こういうの見て
That's right.
そうなんですけど
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ ー、すっげーなー
Wow, this is something really important.
え、これ本当になんか大事なやつだよね
Is it important?
大事なの?
Oh, could you please stop for a second?
あ、ちょっとやめてもらっていいですか?
No, but I like it.
いや、でもね、好きだからさ
Shall we watch it together?
一緒に見る?
I don't watch it.
見ないです
Are you having some kind of trouble?
なんか困ってるとこないの?
No, no.
ないない
Oh, you know, like death at the same time, etc.
あれ、なんかほら、死亡同期とかさ、
You'll be doing interviews and other things, right?
面接とかいろいろやるでしょ?
Wow wow
うわーうわー
Wow.
うわ ー
Oh, that's right.
え、そうだな
What is this?
これ何?
Ah, that's a collection.
あ、それ収集です
collection?
収集?
For your hair.
髪の毛に
hair?
髪の毛?
Or attaching it to the rubber.
ゴムの上にこう、くっつけたりとか
Rubber?
ゴム?
Oh, on the condom?
あ、コンダムの上?
No, it's different.
いや、違って
Oh, will you do it to my dick on top of the condom?
あ、 コンダムの上でじゃあチンコにやってくれるの?
No, um, what are you doing?
違って、えっと、何してるんですか?
I'll have to ask you to do it later.
後でやってもらったらじゃあ
picture?
え?
Eh, is that okay?
え、いいの?
No.
ないです
Please stop.
や めてください
get married.
結 婚する
Hey, hey, hey, here we go for the interview.
え、ねぇねぇねぇ、ほらさ、面接をさ、
That’s it, right?
あれでしょ?
I heard that you would like me to do something for you.
なんかしてほしいって聞いたんだけど
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
I agree.
そうだね
Then I'll interview you.
じゃあ面接してあげるよ
Because I'm a professional interviewer.
面接のプロだから
Ah, yes.
あ、はい
Well then, that's right.
じゃあね、そうだな
So, let's start with size 3.
じゃあ3サイズから聞こうかな
3 sizes.
3サイズ
80...
85?
86?
It's 85.
85だよ
Do you understand?
分かるんですか?
How many cups?
カップ数は?
So how many cups?
じゃあカップ数
Well, B or C.
えっと、BかC
That's nice.
いいねぇ
B or C.
BかC
I like it the most.
一番好き
It smells good.
いい匂いする
Huh?
あれ?
I thought the sweat was soaking in even more,
汗もっと染み込んでるかなと思ったら、
It smells good.
いい匂いするね
Oh, is that so?
え、そうですか?
You do your laundry the way you like.
洗濯好みにしてんだね
Ah, yes.
あ、はい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Festman...
フェストマン...
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
Ah, thank you very much.
あ、ありがとうございます
May I ask you to stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらおうかな
I really want to see them together.
2つ姿ってちゃんと見たいもんね
Ah, just like that.
あー、ほーまるで
yes.
はい
Isn't it the best?
最高じゃないですか
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Maybe I should have it rotate a little more slowly.
ちょっと ゆっくり回転とかしてもらっちゃおうかな
Isn't the skirt a little too long?
ちょっとでもさ、スカート長くない?
Is it long?
長いですか?
I wonder if it's long.
長いかなぁ
Eh, what do you think?
え、どう?
Do you like this personally?
自分的にこれがいい?
Shuff?
シャフ?
No, that's right.
いや、そうですね
Is this what they say in Schaff?
シャフでこう言われてる?
Well, I mean, the whole thing is a little...
いや、ていうか、全体的にもちょっと...
Well, wouldn't something like this be better?
いや、もうこんなのがいいんじゃない?
No, no, I can see it,
いやいやいや、見えちゃいますから、
If you squat down.
しゃがんだら
What, what do you see?
え、何が見えるの?
If you squat down, you can see my panties.
しゃがんだらパンツ見えちゃいます
pants?
パンツ?
You can show me your panties, right?
パンツは見せるもんでしょ
Oh, no.
え、違う
Show me your panties, man, those.
パンツを見せて、男のさ、あれをさ
No, no, no.
いや いやいや
Isn't that how you earn your passing?
そうやって合格を貸してるもんじゃないの?
Please wait.
待ってください
He's a nice guy, isn't he?
ちょろよかな男なんだよね
Huh?
あれ?
You're not wearing pants.
パンツ履いてないじゃん
Oh, wait a minute.
え、ちょっと待って
picture?
え?
Wait, wait, wait.
待って待って待って
I'm not wearing pants though.
パンツ履いてないんだけど
Well, it's a surprise.
え、サプライズじゃん
On the other hand, I was surprised.
逆に俺がびっくりしたよ
Eh, what?
え、なになに?
Why?
どうして?
I was surprised when the manga came out.
漫画出てきてびっくりしたんだけど
No, that's not true.
いや、違うんだよ
What, what is this?
え、これなんすか?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I was super surprised.
超びっくりした
Is that how you created it?
そういう作成なの?
No.
違います
Oh no, she's a femme fatale.
やべえ、魔性の女じゃん
different.
違う
Suddenly, it's a manga.
だ って漫画だよいきなり
Hey.
ねえ
What is that?
なにそれ
It's different.
違うんです
There is a really deep reason for this.
これは本当深いわけがありまして
That's deep.
深いわけね
There's a deep reason.
深 い わけがありまして
I see.
なるほど
Do it like that.
そうやってね
While saying that I can see your panties.
パンツ見えちゃうとか言いながらね
No.
違うよ
Suddenly I showed him a manga.
いきなり漫画見せちゃって
That made me think that this woman was lewd.
それでこの女すけびだなって思わせて
I see.
なるほど
Is that so?
そういうことか
It's so cute.
すけびじゃん
Do you mean momopan pantyhose?
モモパンパンストってことか
Ah, but your legs are long.
あ、でも足長いね
Long legs.
足長い
It tickles.
くすぐっちゃい
I finally feel it more.
いよいよ感じてもっと
It's ticklish and it feels ticklish.
くすぐったいって、くすぐったいって気持ちよ
There’s only one God, right?
神一人でしょ?
That's right.
そうなのね
Oh, that's right.
え、そうなのって
I don't know anything, honestly.
私何も知りませんよ、ぶっちゃって
Very
めちゃ
It's so ticklish.
く ちゃくすぐったい
It's sensitive.
感度がいいんだ
This is what it is now.
これ今あれだからね
Because it's an interview.
面接だから
The interview is this.
面接はね、これ
That's right.
そうだ よ
Do you want to check the sensitivity?
感度チェックってするでしょ?
I won't.
しないですよ
How good is your sensitivity?
あなたの感度はどの程度くらいいいんですかってね
What, are you going to do that?
え、するの?
I do.
しますよね
Do, do, do.
するするする
there is.
あります
There is.
ありますよ
there is.
あります
Is that so?
そんなもん?
そんなもんなの?
It hurts.
痛って
It doesn't hurt too much, does it?
あんまり痛くないでしょ
What, do you like fighting?
え、戦うの好き?
Maybe.
もしかして
Eh, no, no.
え、いや、ないない
It still sounded really good.
今でもめっちゃいい音したよね
Do you like fighting?
戦うの好き?
no.
いや
That's not true.
違 いますよ
Oh, no?
あ、違うの?
Is it different?
違うんですか?
That's not true.
違いますよ
The fact that he's not wearing pants means he's not wearing them either.
パンツ履いてないってことはさ、こっちも付けてないね
No, it's not attached.
いや、付いてない
I don't wear pants, but I do wear a bra.
パンツは履かないけど、ブラが付ける
I really had to own the pants.
パンツは本当に所持上があったんです
In possession?
所持上?
It went up.
上がりました
I guess I gave it to you.
お出ししちゃったんだね
No.
違います
Well then, let's check your bra.
じゃあ、ブラジャーチェックしましょうかね
I don't want to miss this because it will be wasted.
これ、無駄になるから逃したくないんだよな
I want you to wear it all the time.
ずっと着ててほしいの
Do you understand what it means?
意味わかる?
I have a fetish like that.
そういうフェチがあんだよ
I don't know.
わからない
Where is this hitting you now?
これ、今どこ当たってますか?
Is it now?
今ですか?
It's cute covered.
被っちゃって可愛いね
I guess I'll wear it, then.
着ちゃうかな、じゃあ
Oh, I'm wearing it.
あれ、着てる
Well, I'm going to wear it, so I won't.
え、着ちゃいますから着ないです
Is that what you mean?
そういうことなの?
I'm going to wear it.
着 ちゃ うんですよ
It has great defense.
すごい防御が高いな
You're very defensive.
めっちゃ防御してるじゃん
I guess I'll wear it.
着 ちゃうかな
Shall I wear it?
着ちゃう?
I'll wear it.
着ちゃう
You make a cute voice.
可愛い声出しますね
It's not out.
出てないです
Isn't it out?
出てない?
It's not out.
出てないです
This hand is cute.
この手、可愛いね
This is what happens.
こうなっちゃうんだ
I even said it this time.
今回さえ言った
This is how it will turn out.
こうなっちゃうんだね
cute.
可愛い
Isn't it cute?
可愛いじゃないですかね
Do you like ears?
耳好き?
Yeah.
うん
Do you like listening?
耳好きなの?
Because she has a really cute voice.
めっちゃ可愛い声出してるからですね
It's a different voice than before.
さっきの声と違うもん
That's right.
そんなんやろ
Understood.
わかった
I guess you're not wearing pants because you'll get wet easily.
すぐ濡れちゃうから、パンツ履いてないんだね
I see, you'll soon get your pants wet and ruin them.
なるほど、すぐパンツを濡れて壊れちゃうから
Right next to my waist.
すぐ腰のまんこか
That's cool.
やろいね
This line is exactly where it hits the right spot.
ちょうどこの線のところがさ、 いいところに食い込むわけで
Sho.
しょ
What are you going to do?
何 とかするの?
Not much.
あんまり
Not much?
あんまりしない?
That's a lie.
嘘だ
Yeah, I don't, really.
うん、しないです、本当に
I prefer to be seen as a person.
人にされるほうが好きなんだ
Help room.
助け部屋
My hands.
手が
That's erotic.
エロいね
You're erotic.
あなたエロいね
No.
違います
Wow, that's amazing.
わー、なんかすげー
It's slimy here.
ぬるぬるしてる、ここ
Can you figure it out yourself?
自分でわかる?
Try touching it.
触ってみなよ
You still don't know how good masturbation is.
オナニの良さはまだ知らないんだね
Why are you quitting?
なんでやめちゃうの?
Stay still.
いじっとけな
Stay still and practice masturbation.
い じっとけな、オナニの練習
It will be useful for future harvests, if you remember how to masturbate.
今後の収穫にも役立つでしょ、オナニを覚えとけば
It's amazing.
すごいです
I'm good at masturbating.
得意オナニっているよ
There will be more real ones, so one thing.
本物増えるんだから、ひとつ
I won't say it.
言わないですからね
Move it, move it.
動かして、動かして
Touch me where you think it feels good.
気持ちいいと思うところ、触ってこな
There are also such good goods.
こんな良いグッズもあんだよ
Where did you get it from?
どこから持ってきたんですか?
From where?
ど こから?
I had prepared it because I wanted Yumi-chan to be happy.
ユミちゃんに喜んでほしくって用意していたんです
What is this?
なんですか、これ
You don't really know my name.
俺の名前よく知らないんだよね
Masturbation stuff.
オナニーのやつ
It's really exhausting.
めちゃめちゃしんどくる
It's hard.
しんどくるっしょ
What do you think?
どう思う?
If you win this, it will be in a private place.
これ当てたら、民間なところに
Because once you learn how to masturbate, you'll be able to do it by yourself at home.
だってオナニー覚えたら、家で一人でできるようになるんだよ
If you think about it, wouldn't it be better to memorize it?
そう考えたら覚えた方が良くない?
Or maybe there's someone who will always do it for you.
それとも、常にやってくれる人がいるから、
You can't seem to do it yourself?
自分でやりそうにないって?
I'm begging you.
せがくて
What's going on with this?
これどうなってんの?
Hide it well.
頑丈に隠すね
Even though I'm not wearing anything underneath.
下は履いてないくせに
I'll help you.
助けちゃうから
I'm not wearing anything underneath, so there's nothing convincing about it.
下は履いてないから、なんの説得力もないよ
Oh, amazing.
あ、すげ
It quickly became hard.
しっくりがすぐ固くなった
Is it correct?
当たってます?
I'd like to see what happens.
どうなってるか見てみたいね
You can't really see through pantyhose.
パンスト越しだとよく見えないからね
I don't know why it's wet though.
濡れてるのは分かんないけどさ
Look.
ほ ら
It grows.
伸びるもん
Wow, my pussy is so coated.
すげえマンコ塗れてる
why?
なんで?
Look.
ほ ら
Don't you like this kind of thing?
こういうの好きなんじゃないの?
This is how it's done.
こうやってされるの
It's different.
ちがうよ
picture?
え?
different?
ちがう?
Isn't there a difference?
ちがうくないんじゃない?
It got really bad.
すごくなっちゃった
Wow, so wet.
うわー、超濡れてる
Oh no.
やば